free-merchants.com 2016-12-04

# free-merchants.com - Privatepolicing

We use cookies to enhance your visit to our site and to bring you advertisements that might interest you. Read our Privacy Policy to find out more. Ok

**Privacy Statement Free-Merchants Group**

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy statement explains what personal information we collect and how we use this data. Please review the following information:  
This privacy policy sets out how Free-Merchants Group uses and protects any information that you give Free-Merchants Group when you use this website.  
Free-Merchants Group is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
Free-Merchants Group may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information:  
\- name and job title  
\- contact information including email address  
\- demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
\- other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

**Internal record keeping.**

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Protection of minors**

Services provided by the Company are not intended for or directed to minors or persons under the legal age. Any person who provides personal information to us, presents us with the information that they have 18 years or more in their jurisdiction. We reserve the right to access and verify personal information provided by you. If we become aware that a minor was trying to provide or submit personal information, we can not accept this information and may take steps to remove such information from our database.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing: [admin@free-merchants.com](mailto:admin@free-merchants.com)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

**Updating this Policy**

We reserve the right to revise this policy from time to time. Any changes to this Policy will be posted on the website. Subscribe to the website or the regular use of means that you agree with the policy with all the changes. You should regularly re-read the text of the Policy. You can contact us by e-mail if you have any questions about this Policy.
